Finding Aid for Ivory Photo, Ann Arbor, Michigan ca. 1927-1971
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives-- 4"x5"
  - Ypsilanti
    - Schools
      - Cleary College
        - Commencement 1937-1939, 1941, 19 negatives (Box 24)
        - Dances and Parties 1937-1940, 32 negatives (Box 24)
        - Orchestras 1937-1938, 2 negatives (Box 24)
        - Students and Faculty
          - In classrooms (at typewriters and adding machines) June 15, 1937, 6 negatives (Box 24)
          - Education short course group July 7, 1937 (Box 24)
          - In hallway between classes May 10, 1939 (Box 24)
          - Men's union May 16, 1939 (Box 24)
          - In classes, library, bowling, relaxing May 8, 1940, 19 negatives (Box 24)
          - Coed circa 1940, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Eastern Michigan University (Michigan State Normal College)
        - Windstorm damage August 1, 1940, 5 negatives (Box 24)
        - Alumni Building (?) circa 1940 (Box 24)
        - Kitchen in girls' dormitory June 19, 1958, 4 negatives (Box 24)
    - Street and Buildings
      - Briggs Stadium -- under construction July 20, 1937, 6 negatives (Box 24)
      - Ypsilanti Field House -- construction August 23, 1937 (Box 24)
      - Water tower circa 1940 (Box 24)
      - Ypsilanti Field House -- interior 1955 (Box 24)
      - Downtown April 24, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Unidentified February 28, 1966, 3 negatives (Box 24)
  - Washtenaw County
    - Aerial Views 1963, 1968, 4 negatives (Box 24)
    - Businesses
      - Albin Grocery Store September 18, 1959, 3 negatives (Box 24)
      - Scholtz Farm Supply 1951, 4 negatives (Box 24)
      - Twist Grocery November 1, 1938 (Box 24)
    - Cassidy Lake Tech -- glider, log cabin, students 1941, 28 negatives (Box 24)
    - County Offices
      - Road Commission -- trucks April 30, 1957 (Box 24)
      - Sheriff's Department
        - Dinner at jail December 29, 1941, 3 negatives (Box 24)
        - Junior deputies (boys) April 5, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 24)
    - Farms
      - Dhu Varren Horse Farm August 12, 1937, 7 negatives (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous 1954-1955, 5 negatives (Box 24)
    - Lakes
      - Fish Lake 1952, 4 negatives (Box 24)
      - Horseshoe Lake 1952 (Box 24)
      - Portage Lake -- boats, early 1960s, 6 negatives (Box 24)
    - Rural Scenes
      - Belelville Road 1953 (Box 24)
      - Chelsea area? 1941, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Dexter Road 1954 (Box 24)
      - Geddes and Dixboro Roads 1956, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Lohr Road(J. Raleigh Nelson house) 1939, 3 negatives (Box 24)
      - Scio Church and Wagner Roads 1957, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Steen Road 1953 (Box 24)
      - U.S. 12 1951, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - U.S. 16 1953, 3 negatives (Box 24)
      - U.S. 23 1951-1956, 19 negatives (Box 24)
      - Wagner Road 1948, 1953, 4 negatives (Box 24)
      - Waters Road (Morton Cox house) 1956 (Box 24)
      - Unidentified -- near Glencoe Hills Riding Stables 1952 (Box 24)
  - Michigan Towns and Counties (non Washtenaw)
    - Belleville
      - People's State Bank 1951-1952, 4 negatives (Box 24)
    - Big Rapids
      - Ferris Institute circa 1940 (Box 24)
    - Brighton
      - Cole, Linda circa 1951, 2 negatives (Box 24)
    - Brooklyn
      - Carbeck house and apartment 1959, 2 negatives (Box 24)
    - Cadillac
      - Bendle, C.L., Memorials -- truck 1951 (Box 24)
    - Clinton
      - Road circa 1952, 4 negatives (Box 24)
    - Detroit
      - Airport -- interior 1949 (Box 24)
      - Belle Isle -- with picnickers July 12, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Bob-Lo boats and Detroit skyline 1940s (Box 24)
      - Douglas Gregory and Associates (auto accessory distributors) 1953 (Box 24)
      - Maccabees Life Insurance Company 1956, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Solvental Chemical Products -- interior and employees 1950, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Sunshine Biscuits, Inc. -- display 1951 (Box 24)
      - Wolverine Potato Chips -- grocery store display 1955 (Box 24)
    - Dundee
      - Dundee Plastic Plant -- interior 1967, 4 negatives (Box 25)
      - Uniloy plant -- interior with workers 1967, 18 negatives (Box 25)
    - Flint
      - Factory interior with worker 1957 (Box 25)
    - Garden City
      - Minder Drugs 1950s (Box 25)
      - Rexall Drug Store 1953 (Box 25)
    - Grosse Pointe
      - Party tents, early 1960s, 11 negatives (Box 25)
    - Hamburg
      - Brown McLaren Manufacturing Company -- interior with employees 1954, 6 negatives (Box 25)
      - Super Alloy Forge -- equipment and workers 1962, 7 negatives (Box 25)
    - Jonesville
      - Andrew Mack and Son -- products 1954 (Box 25)
    - Lansing
      - Michigan Congress of Parents and Teachers -- meeting 1956 (Box 25)
      - Street scene -- 1930s (Box 25)
    - Mount Pleasant
      - Oil wells and workers 1939, 3 negatives (Box 25)
    - Oak Grove
      - Oak Grove Standard station 1955 (Box 25)
    - Oxford
      - Syncro, Inc. -- machinery circa 1957, 5 negatives (Box 25)
    - Pinckney
      - Post Office and storefront circa 1955 (Box 25)
    - Royal Oak
      - Sherman Products, Inc. -- interior with workers circa 1948, 4 negatives (Box 25)
    - Rushton
      - Railroad bridge and pond July 22, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 25)
    - South Lyon
      - Michigan Seamless Tube -- exterior and interior with workers 1954, 7 negatives (Box 25)
    - Tecumseh
      - High School -- interior 1957, 3 negatives (Box 25)
      - Kitchen 1955 (Box 25)
    - Wayne
      - Gas plant -- exterior and interior 1956, 19 negatives (Box 25)
      - Northside Hardware 1950s (Box 25)
      - Shifrin Jewelers 1950s (Box 25)
      - Wayne Iron Works -- interior with workers circa 1956, 3 negatives (Box 25)
      - Wedding (Brown) circa 1956, 9 negatives (Box 25)
    - Wayne County
      - I-94 1960s, 6 negatives (in 3 envelope) (Box 25)
      - Storefronts -- Nugent Hardware; Hamiln's Locker Service; George Sayre, M.D.; Reo Hotel; Humphries Men's Wear 1950s, 3 negatives (Box 25)
      - Wayne County General Hospital -- heart pump circa 1963, 5 negatives (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Buildings and Views
      - Buhrman (Florence and Lou) house -- interior and exterior 1948, 18 negatives (Box 25)
      - Demaris house -- aerial 1968, 3 negatives (in 2 envelope) (Box 25)
      - Langford houses 1938, 5 negatives (Box 25)
      - Owen (Dr. Floyd) house -- interior 1955, 2 negatives (Box 25)
      - Tower 1930s (Box 25)
      - Trailer Camp 1942, 3 negatives (Box 25)
    - Businesses
      - Aero Engineering -- staff December 1941 (Box 25)
      - American Type Founders -- interior with workers 1951, 2 negatives (Box 25)
      - Bank -- interior 1951, 3 negatives (Box 25)
      - Bob-o-Link golf (Box 25)
      - Cheek, Lawrence -- lapidarist 1954, 2 negatives (Box 25)
      - Cribley and Son -- tractor 1960 (Box 25)
      - Custom Built Shoe Company -- interior 1939 (Box 25)
      - Davis finger guards 1953, 3 negatives (Box 25)
      - Earle Equipment Company 1954, 7 negatives (Box 25)
      - G and M Products (housewares) 1956, 3 negatives (Box 25)
      - Gould, H. -- woman with photostat machine 1951 (Box 25)
      - Gudeman Company -- machinery 1955, 4 negatives (Box 25)
      - Hackney's Hardware -- interior 1955 (Box 25)
      - Hamaher, A.C., Company -- electric calendar and wire splicer 1953, 7 negatives (Box 25)
      - Ramsay Drugs -- interior and exterior with druggist; Kroger Meats; Red Front Market circa 1940, 3 negatives (Box 25)
      - Rolly's Landscape Service 1954, 2 negatives (Box 25)
      - Shoe store window display, Mishawaka, Indiana 1948 (Box 25)
      - Soda fountain 1951 (Box 25)
      - Soda shop circa 1938 (Box 25)
    - Churches
      - St. Thomas Lutheran -- confirmation and baptism? 1954, 6 negatives (Box 25)
    - Events
      - Baker, Betty, trial January 17, 1937, 7 negatives (Box 25)
      - Beauty contest circa 1950, 4 negatives (Box 25)
      - Booth Fellowship in Architecture 1937, 3 negatives (Box 25)
    - People
      - Archduke Otto and Rudolph (at University of Michigan) January 9, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 25)
      - Eskimos circa 1966, 8 negatives (Box 25)
      - Henie, Sonia January 7, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 25)
      - Nagel, Barney -- Detroit News photographer at work, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 25)
      - Russell, Jane circa 1954 (Box 25)
      - University of Wisconsin, Local 50, early 1960s (Box 25)
- Negatives-- 5"x7"
  - Ann Arbor
    - Buildings and Views
      - Airports and Airplanes
        - Hammond Aircraft, planes and workshop April 20, 1934, 9 negatives (Box 25)
      - Churches
        - First Methodist Church, State Street
          - Architect's rendering circa 1940 (Box 26)
          - Exterior and interior circa 1946, 3 negatives (Box 26)
        - Lutheran Student Chapel -- blueprints 1949 (Box 26)
        - University Lutheran Chapel, 1511 Washtenaw -- exterior and interior circa 1957, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Hospitals
        - Mercywood Sanitarium September 14, 1935 (Box 26)
        - St. Joseph's Hospital -- aerial view 1932 (Box 26)
      - Houses and Businesses
        - Devonshire
          - 2023 -- Lucy Lewis house October 4, 1934, 3 negatives (Box 26)
          - 2121 -- house December 24, 1933 (Box 26)
        - Fair Oaks Parkway -- 1126 -- Emory Hyde house July 3, 1934 (Box 26)
        - Forest Court? -- 1324 June 28, 1934 (Box 26)
        - Fountain -- 1306 -- Fred T. Stowe house, exterior and interior circa 1935, 5 negatives (Box 26)
        - Green Street - house September 19, 1933 (Box 26)
        - Heatherway at Arlington -- Huron Hills Country Club July 25, 1936 (Box 26)
        - Huron, 344 -- Ann Arbor News building circa 1937, 3 negatives (Box 26)
        - Main, North, at Catherine -- United States Post Office September 14, 1935 (Box 26)
        - Main, South
          - 106 -- Peck's Drug Store, interior (Box 26)
          - 201-203 -- First National Bank Building September 17, 1935 (Box 26)
          - 1035 -- Mrs. John Green house? March 26, 1957 (Box 26)
          - at Liberty April 8, 1933 (Box 26)
        - Maynard, 311 -- University Press 1931, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Packard, 2301 -- Anderson house June 28, 1934 (Box 26)
        - Ross, 605-611 -- Ann Arbor Home Builders 1948-1949, 4 negatives (Box 26)
        - State Street, South
          - 900 -- G.F. Gratton Drugs, early 1930s (Box 26)
          - at North University 1931-1933, 3 negatives (Box 26)
        - Unidentified houses 1930s-1950s, 17 negatives (Box 26)
      - Railroad Station and Trains
        - Ann Arbor Railroad Station circa 1936 (Box 26)
        - Train wrecks 1930s, 3 negatives (Box 26)
      - Schools
        - Ann Arbor High School 1930s (Box 26)
        - Ashley Street Nursery School -- interior May 30, 1936, 3 negatives (Box 26)
        - Bach School November 1, 1937 (Box 26)
        - Eberwhite School circa May 13, 1960, 3 negatives (Box 26)
        - Perry School November 1, 1937 (Box 26)
        - Slauson Junior High School 1938, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Tappan Junior High School November 1, 1937 (Box 26)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Ann Arbor Skyline from West Park September 14, 1935 (Box 26)
        - Windmill -- off Huron and 9th July 25, 1936, 3 negatives (Box 26)
    - Businesses
      - Anicka, Walter T. -- architectural drawings 1948-1950, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Arnesen, Ragnar -- architectural drawings 1948-1950, 14 negatives (Box 26)
      - Buhr Machine Tool Company -- machinery 1953, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Gratton Drug Store December 20, 1934, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Hard and Company -- machinery May 5, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Hobbs and Schmidt, Realtors and Builders -- model homes 1953 (Box 26)
      - Ivory Photo - Mel Ivory and chemical shelf May 20, 1934 (Box 26)
      - King-Seeley Corporation
        - Product (governor) 1942 (Box 26)
        - Products 1947, 5 negatives (Box 26)
        - Architect's drawing for new plant 1948 (Box 26)
        - Employees? circa 1957 (Box 26)
      - Loree and Sirrin -- architectural drawing 1948 (Box 26)
      - Metals Recovery Company 1948-1949 (Box 26)
      - National Sanitation Foundation -- staff, rats November 21, 1946, 5 negatives (Box 26)
      - Physicists Research Company -- profilometer August 13, 1969 (Box 26)
      - Schaible Motor Sales February 22, 1934, 3 negatives (Box 26)
    - Motor Vehicles
      - Cars circa 1929, 12 negatives (Box 26)
      - Race car April 20, 1929 (Box 26)
      - Thayer, R.P., Distributors (Rain-Beau Fishing Lines -- truck circa 1950, 2 negatives (Box 26)
    - Organizations and Groups
      - Boys with model airplanes
        - circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - circa 1936 at University High (Box 26)
      - Mack, Dr. Harry, and group collecting old shoes circa 1938, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Theater Crafts -- 35th Anniversary 1949 (Box 26)
    - People
      - Allard, Rob 1950 (Box 26)
      - Baldwin mother and children circa 1948, 3 negatives (Box 26)
      - Cannon, George -- in Marine uniform January 9, 1942 (Box 26)
      - Farkas, Mary and Stephen -- Christmas card 1948 (Box 26)
      - Jenkins, Mrs. Bruce -- baby December 13, 1948 (Box 26)
      - Metzger, Walt -- children November 12, 1953 (Box 26)
      - Preiskorn, Erwin Ottmer circa 1951 (Box 26)
      - Stickney, Al 1950, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Stoddard, John, at class reunion, with two unidentified men June 21, 1930 (Box 26)
      - Unidentified
        - Women and man circa 1920s, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Children in wicker buggy, girl on tricycle circa 1930, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Boy with camera October 24, 1931 (Box 26)
        - Couple at piano circa 1930-1935 (Box 26)
        - Man by boxcar ("railroad bum") 1930s (Box 26)
    - Social Life and Customs
      - Sports
        - German-Clague baseball team circa 1940, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Weddings 1950, 2 negatives (Box 26)
  - University of Michigan
    - Alumni Activities
      - Commemorative plates -- Angell Hall and Law School 1929, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Law School reunion, Class of 1895 February 18, 1935 (Box 26)
    - Athletics
      - Men's
        - Basketball January 1931, 5 negatives (Box 26)
        - Fencing January 16, 1930, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Football
          - Freshman football squad November 15, 1929 (Box 26)
          - Benny Oosterbaan and Mr. Hatch circa 1936 (Box 26)
          - Fritz Crisler in office February 27, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Gymnastics 1930s (Box 26)
        - Soccer team -- Chinese June 12, 1939 (Box 26)
        - Wrestling undated, 4 negatives (Box 26)
      - Women's
        - Bowling 1930s, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Fencing circa 1930s, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Field Hockey 1930s (Box 26)
        - Golf circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - Rifle team circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - Softball 1930s (Box 26)
        - Swimming 1930s, 3 negatives (Box 26)
        - Volleyball 1930s (Box 26)
        - Wrestling, undated, 4 negatives (Box 26)
    - Buildings and Views
      - Alumni Memorial Hall
        - Thomas Benton exhibit December 12, 1931 (Box 26)
        - Exterior, 1935- circa 1938, 4 negatives (Box 26)
      - Anatomy Laboratory (interior) January 5, 1932, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Angell Hall
        - circa 1928-1930s, 6 negatives (Box 26)
        - Aerial view circa 1938 (Box 26)
          [see also 4"x5" negative]
      - Architecture Building
        - Architecture library interior September 28, 1929 (Box 26)
        - circa 1930, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - circa 1937 (Box 26)
      - Athletic Administration Building circa 1940 (Box 26)
      - Barbour (Betsy) Dormitory August 31, 1935 (Box 26)
      - Barbour Gymnasium circa 1930 (Box 26)
      - Burton Tower June 1, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Campus Scenes
        - Walks near physics and engineering buildings circa 1928, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Students near State Street and North University circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - Sidewalk near Natural Science building and aerial view July 25, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - the Mall: Burton tower and rackham June 21, 1938 (Box 26)
        - Rackham and Burton Tower; Carl Milles fountain near League circa 1938, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Chemistry Building August 31, 1935 (Box 26)
      - Clements Library September 11, 1935, 4 negatives (Box 26)
      - Cook (Martha) dormitory
        - Women in Blue Room circa 1932 (Box 26)
          [See also 8x10 prints]
        - circa 1935 (Box 26)
        - July 25, 1936 (Box 26)
        - November 19, 1941 (Box 26)
      - Couzens Hall -- dormitory
        - circa 1930 garden (Box 26)
        - September 11, 1935 (Box 26)
      - Dental Building
        - circa 1930, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - August 31, 1935 (Box 26)
        - circa 1935 (Box 26)
        - Summer circa 1938 (Box 26)
        - Kellogg Institute April 15, 1940 (Box 26)
      - Economics Building circa 1930 (Box 26)
      - Engineering
        - East Hall circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - West Engineering Arch September 2, 1935, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - West Engineering Annex -- with clock tower and Mechanical Laboratory -- Automobile Division
          - circa 1930, 2 negatives (Box 26)
          - July 25, 1936 (Box 26)
      - Ferry Field and stands circa 1930, 3 negatives (Box 26)
      - Fountains. (Box 26)
        (See: UM-Buildings and Views -- Campus Scenes)
      - Fraternities and Sororities
        - Alpha Chi Rho circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - Alpha Phi (1830 Hill Street) circa 1930 (Box 26)
          [see also 4"x5" negatives]
        - Alpha Chi Sigma 1930s (Box 26)
        - Alpha Epsilon Phi 1930s (Box 26)
        - Beta Theta Pi (604 South State) circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - Delta Delta Delta June 11, 1931 (Box 26)
        - Delta Phi circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - Delta Tau Delta circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - Phi Beta Pi (1010 East Ann) 1930s, 2 negatives (Box 26)
        - Psi Upsilon circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - Sigma Alpha Epsilon circa 1930 (Box 26)
        - Zeta Tau Alpha circa 1930 (Box 26)
      - Health Service
        - Old building circa 1928 (Box 26)
        - New building April 15, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Hill Auditorium 1930s, 3 negatives (Box 26)
      - Intramural Sports Building
        - circa 1927 (Box 26)
        - circa May 1928, 3 negatives (Box 26)
        - circa 1930, 3 negatives (Box 26)
        - circa 1935, 2 negatives (Box 26)
      - Laundry -- interior with workers February 29, 1928, 3 negatives (Box 26)
      - Law School
        - Hutchins Hall circa 1930 (Box 27)
        - Law Quad -- various views circa 1928-circa1939, 17 negatives (Box 27)
        - Lawyers Club -- dining hall, lounge, exterior circa 1930, 6 negatives (Box 27)
      - Legal Research Building (Library)
        - Exterior
          - circa 1927-1935, 9 negatives (Box 27)
          - November 30, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 27)
        - Interior circa 1930-1935, 5 negatives (Box 27)
      - Old Law Building
        - Exterior circa 1930 (Box 27)
        - Library -- interior, 1929- circa 1930, 3 negatives (Box 27)
      - Library, Graduate
        - Reading room July 1929 (Box 27)
        - circa 1930 (Box 27)
        - August 30, 1935 (Box 27)
        - Drawing June 1, 1941 (Box 27)
      - Medical Building
        (See also: Anatomy Laboratory)
        - September 5, 1935 (Box 27)
        - September 11, 1935 (Box 27)
      - Michigan League
        - Construction October 28, 1928 (Box 27)
        - Construction circa 1928 (Box 27)
        - Drinking fountain January 6, 1930 (Box 27)
        - circa 1930, 3 negatives (Box 27)
        - November 23, 1935 (Box 27)
        - May 25, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 27)
        - circa June 1937 (Box 27)
      - Michigan Union
        - April 23, 1929 (Box 27)
        - September 11, 1935, 2 negatives (Box 27)
      - Morris Hall July 25 1936, March 1929 (Box 27)
      - Mosher-Jordan dormitory
        - September 3, 1935 (Box 27)
        - circa 1935 (Box 27)
        - July 25, 1936 (Box 27)
      - Museum of Anthropology -- interior and Benjamin March (research associate) 1930s, 3 negatives (Box 27)
      - Natural Science Building circa 1935 (Box 27)
      - Newberry (Helen) dormitory
        - circa 1930 (Box 27)
        - October 19, 1936 (Box 27)
      - Observatory 1930s, 2 negatives (Box 27)
      - Palmer Field and dormitories
        - circa 1930 (Box 27)
        - July 25, 1936 (Box 27)
      - Pharmacology Building
        - early 1930s (Box 27)
        - July 25, 1936 (Box 27)
      - Physics
        - Randall Laboratory (East Physics) circa 1930, 3 negatives (Box 27)
        - West Physics circa 1930, 2 negatives (Box 27)
      - President's House
        - circa 1930 (Box 27)
        - September 1, 1935 (Box 27)
        - September 12, 1935 (Box 27)
      - Rackham
        - Stone panels March 8, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 27)
        - September 11, 1937 (Box 27)
        - Exterior and interiors circa 1938, 6 negatives (Box 27)
      - Simpson Memorial Institute
        - circa 1930 (Box 27)
        - September 12, 1935 (Box 27)
      - Stadium
        - circa 1930, 7 negatives (Box 27)
        - Neal and Olds at stadium circa 1938 (Box 27)
      - Student Publications Building circa 1930, 2 negatives (Box 27)
      - Tappan Hall
        - March 1939 (Box 27)
        - Entry, undated (Box 27)
      - University Elementary School
        - July 25, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 27)
        - circa 1938 (Box 27)
      - University Hospital
        - South Department and Annex September 8, 1928 (Box 27)
        - Boys' workshop March 25, 1929, 2 negatives (Box 27)
        - Feature on artificial limbs October 10, 1929, 2 negatives (Box 27)
        - circa 1930, 3 negatives (Box 27)
        - Hospital and Observatory October 24, 1931 (Box 27)
        - August 30, 1935 (Box 27)
        - Aerial view circa 1938 (Box 27)
      - University Museums Building circa 1928 (Box 27)
      - Waterman Gym
        - September 20, 1928 (Box 27)
        - circa 1930, 3 negatives (Box 27)
      - West Quad
        - circa 1930 (Box 27)
        - Aerial View 1930s (Box 27)
        - circa 1938 (Box 27)
        - Murfin Gate 1939 (Box 27)
      - Women's Athletic Building
        - circa 1930 (Box 27)
        - September 1, 1935 (Box 27)
      - Yost Field House circa 1930 (Box 27)
    - Colleges, Schools, and Other Divisions
      - Architecture and Design, College of
        - Art students drawing on lawn of law quad July 1928 (Box 27)
        - Warner, Sidney -- Instructor in Decorative Design -- designs May 17, 1941, 7 negatives (Box 27)
      - Forestry, School of -- truck and students circa 1920 (Box 27)
      - Library Extension Service
        - Offices and personnel October 8, 1928, 2 negatives (Box 27)
        - Offices, exhibit, personnel 1946, 3 negatives (Box 27)
      - Medical School -- anatomy lesson, late 19th or early 20th century (Box 27)
      - Michigan Historical Collections -- exhibit November 13, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 27)
      - Physics symposium
        - July 20, 1929, 2 negatives (Box 27)
        - Summer 1931 (Box 27)
        - July 25, 1932, 2 negatives (Box 27)
        - July 10, 1933 (Box 27)
        - July 27, 1934 (Box 27)
        - July 19, 1935 (Box 27)
        - July 22, 1936 (Box 27)
        - July 31, 1941 (Box 27)
      - University Elementary School? -- Miss Agnes True, child psychologist -- in office and laboratory September 4, 1934, 5 negatives (Box 27)
      - University Museums -- displays, summer 1938, 3 negatives (Box 27)
    - Individuals and Groups
      - Administration and Faculty
        - Clements?, William L. March 23, 1928, 2 negatives (Box 27)
        - Cross, Arthur Lyon circa 1938, 3 negatives (Box 27)
        - Griffin, Clare -acting dean School of business Administration January 10, 1928, 3 negatives (Box 27)